const data = [
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950093",
      "correctAnswer": "Baseball",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Football",
        "Basketball",
        "Ice Hockey"
      ],
      "question": "This sport is called the \"American pastime\"?",
      "tags": [
        "usa",
        "general_knowledge",
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950047",
      "correctAnswer": "Adolf Hitler",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Josef Stalin",
        "Joseph Goebbels",
        "Hans von Tschammer und Osten"
      ],
      "question": "Who was supposed to present Jesse Owens his 100 metre Gold Medal at the Berlin Olympics?",
      "tags": [
        "olympics",
        "people",
        "general_knowledge",
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "63a03999c7d86251f9b65c8c",
      "correctAnswer": "Settlers of Catan",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Risk",
        "Monopoly",
        "Clue"
      ],
      "question": "In which classic board game do players build roads, villages and cities to collect resources?",
      "tags": [
        "board_games"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "63a03997c7d86251f9b65c89",
      "correctAnswer": "Sorry!",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Monopoly",
        "Chess",
        "Connect Four"
      ],
      "question": "What is the name of the classic board game where players must move pieces around a board in an effort to get all their pieces \"home\" first?",
      "tags": [
        "board_games"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "62417d160f96c4efe8d773a3",
      "correctAnswer": "Detroit Pistons",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Detroit Dolphins",
        "Detroit Nuggets",
        "Detroit Real"
      ],
      "question": "Which of these is a basketball team based in Detroit?",
      "tags": [
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f85c",
      "correctAnswer": "Football",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Swimming",
        "Tennis",
        "Golf"
      ],
      "question": "With which sport is Wayne Rooney associated?",
      "tags": [
        "football",
        "people",
        "soccer",
        "uk",
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "63a03977c7d86251f9b65c62",
      "correctAnswer": "Clue",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Checkers",
        "Backgammon",
        "Scrabble"
      ],
      "question": "What is the name of the classic board game where players must discover the circumstances of a murder?",
      "tags": [
        "board_games"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "6242e833a22452794eaef207",
      "correctAnswer": "The Canaries",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "The Tigers",
        "The Foxes",
        "The Posh"
      ],
      "question": "What is the nickname of the English football team Norwich City?",
      "tags": [
        "football",
        "uk",
        "soccer",
        "nicknames",
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950080",
      "correctAnswer": "Steeple Chase",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Marathon",
        "Triathlon",
        "Iron Man"
      ],
      "question": "What Type Of Race Got Its Name From A Short Dash Between 2 Churches?",
      "tags": [
        "olympics",
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Sport & Leisure",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9500c1",
      "correctAnswer": "Five",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Six",
        "Seven",
        "Eight"
      ],
      "question": "How Many Players Are In A Basketball Team?",
      "tags": [
        "sport"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    }
  ]

  export default data